<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Simple-Object Web API Reference on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/</link><description>Recent content in Simple-Object Web API Reference on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Container Operations</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/container-operations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/container-operations/</guid><description>Containers resemble Amazon S3 buckets, but unlike S3 buckets, containers can be used to store any type of data. Containers are created and managed either from the dashboard or by using the RESTful Containers Management API [Beta]. You can also perform some container operations through the Simple-Object Web API:
GET Service — lists the containers that are visible to the user who sent the request, according to its tenant.</description></item><item><title>Data-Object Operations</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/data-object-operations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/data-object-operations/</guid><description>To work with data, of any format, as a simple data object, first retrieve the container objects using the GET Container operation, and then use the following S3-like RESTful API object operations:
GET Object — retrieves an object from a container. DELETE Object — deletes an object from a container. PUT Object — adds a new object to a container, or appends data to an existing object.</description></item><item><title>Overview of the Simple-Objet Web API</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/simple-object-web-api/overview/</guid><description>Introduction The platform's Simple-Object Web API enables working with data containers and performing simple data-object operations via a RESTful interface that resembles Amazon's Simple Storage Service (S3) API. In addition to the S3-like capabilities, the Simple-Object Web API enables appending data to existing objects (see Appending Data).
For information on how to secure your Simple-Object Web API requests — including support for HTTPS and HTTP user-authentication methods — see Securing Your Web-API Requests.</description></item></channel></rss>