<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Version 3.0 Release Notes on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/</link><description>Recent content in Version 3.0 Release Notes on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 3.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/v3.0.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/v3.0.0/</guid><description>This document outlines the main additions and changes to the Iguazio MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) in version 3.0.0, and known issues in this version.
Tech Preview NoteThe &amp;quot;[Tech Preview]&amp;quot; notation marks features that are included in the current release as a sneak peek to future release features but without official support in this release. Note that Tech Preview features don't go through QA cycles and might result in unexpected behavior.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.0.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/v3.0.2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/v3.0.2/</guid><description>This document outlines the main additions and changes to the Iguazio MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) in version 3.0.2, and known issues in this version.
Highlights The following are the main highlights of this release:
Extended support for Amazon EKS deployments including auto scale up and down, support for one secondary node group, and attaching services to a specific EKS node group. New Features and Enhancements Deployment Specifications</description></item><item><title>Version 3.0.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/v3.0.3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/release-notes/version-3.0/v3.0.3/</guid><description>This document outlines the main additions and changes to the Iguazio MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) in version 3.0.3, and known issues in this version.
Highlights The following are the main highlights of this release: - Support Spot instances for EKS - Support Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) - Node Selector to assign MLRun jobs and functions to specific nodes - Support GCP GPU machine types -- New Features and Enhancements Deployment Specifications Deployment Specifications Cloud Deployments Support Spot instances for EKS.</description></item></channel></rss>