<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RESTful Web-API References on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/</link><description>Recent content in RESTful Web-API References on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/data-layer/reference/web-apis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data-Service Web-API General Structure</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/data-service-web-api-gen-struct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/data-service-web-api-gen-struct/</guid><description>The data-service web APIs enable complex manipulation of specific data types. These APIs include the Streaming Web API Reference and the NoSQL Web API Reference.
Request Syntax The data-service API operations are HTTP requests that you send to the web-APIs (web-gateway) service of a platform tenant using the PUT or POST HTTP method. The operation to perform is specified within an X-v3io-function HTTP header. Data parameters (where required) are passed within the request's HTTP body, in JSON format.</description></item><item><title>Securing Your Web-API Requests</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/security/</guid><description>Overview You must authenticate your web-API requests to confirm the identity of the sender. You can do this by using any of the supported HTTP user-authentication methods. To further secure your requests, it's recommended that you also use the HTTPS protocol.
HTTPS Requests The web APIs support sending secure requests using the HTTP Secure (HTTPS) protocol (also known as HTTP over TLS), as defined in the RFC 2818 specification. To send an HTTPS request, simply use an https:// IP address in the request URL.</description></item><item><title>Overview of the Web APIs</title><link>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/web-apis/overview/</guid><description>The platform provides the following web APIs:
Simple-Object Web API Reference for working with data as simple data objects using an S3-like interface.
Data-service web APIs for complex manipulation of specific data types (see the Data-Service Web-API General Structure section for high-level structure and syntax details) —
Streaming Web API Reference for working with data streams.
NoSQL Web API Reference for working with NoSQL data objects.</description></item></channel></rss>