<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sessions API on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/sessions-api/</link><description>Recent content in Sessions API on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/sessions-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create Session</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/sessions-api/create-session/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/sessions-api/create-session/</guid><description>Description Creates a new management session. The operation returns a session cookie that can be used to authenticate the user when sending other management requests (see the description of the &amp;lt;cookie&amp;gt; parameter in the General Management-API Structure documentation).
The cookie is valid for the duration of its time-to-live (TTL) period, which is returned in the operation's response (both in the max-age parameter of the Set-Cookie response header, and in the ttl response-data attribute).</description></item><item><title>Overview of the Sessions Management API</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/sessions-api/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/sessions-api/overview/</guid><description>The platform's Sessions Management API (&amp;quot;the Sessions API&amp;quot;) is used to support user authentication and authorization. The management-API operations (except where otherwise specified) authenticate the sender by requiring a session cookie, and authorize the sender to perform the operation based on the authentication results. You acquire this cookie by using the Session API's Create Session operation.
The Sessions API is part of the cluster-management APIs and conforms to the related structure and syntax rules — see General Management-API Structure.</description></item></channel></rss>