<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Time-Series Database (TSDB) Backend on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/</link><description>Recent content in Time-Series Database (TSDB) Backend on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>create Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/create/</guid><description>Description Creates a new TSDB table.
Syntax create(backend, table, if_exists=FAIL, **kw) The following syntax statement replaces the kw parameter with the additional keyword arguments that can be passed for the NoSQL backend via this parameter:
create(backend, table, if_exists=FAIL, rate[, aggregates, aggregation_granularity]) NoteThe method has additional parameters that aren't currently supported for the TSDB backend. Therefore, when calling the method, be sure to explicitly specify the names of all parameters after table.</description></item><item><title>delete Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/delete/</guid><description>Description Deletes a TSDB table or or specific table items.
NoteWhen no filter parameter is set (start, end, filter, or metrics), the entire TSDB table and its schema file (.schema) are deleted.
Syntax delete(backend, table[, filter=&amp;#39;&amp;#39;, start=&amp;#39;&amp;#39;, end=&amp;#39;&amp;#39;, if_missing=FAIL, metrics=[]]) Parameters backend | end | if_missing | start | table
backend The backend type — &amp;quot;tsdb&amp;quot; for the TSDB backend. See Backend Types.
Type: str Requirement: Required table The relative path to the backend data — a directory in the target data container (as configured for the client object) that represents a TSDB table.</description></item><item><title>Overview of the Frames TSDB Backend</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/overview/</guid><description>Introduction The TSDB backend of the Frames API supports Client methods and commands for working with time-series databases (TSDBs). For more information, see also Time-Series Databases (TSDB).
To create a new TSDB table, use the create method.
To add (ingest) items to a TSDB table, use the write method.
To retrieve (consume) items from a TSDB table, use the read method.
To delete a TSDB table or specific table items, use the delete method.</description></item><item><title>read Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/read/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/read/</guid><description>Description Reads (consumes) data from a TSDB table into pandas DataFrames.
Aggregation Queries A TSDB query can include aggregation functions (&amp;quot;aggregators&amp;quot;) to apply to the sample metrics; for a list of the supported aggregation functions, see the description of the aggregators parameter. To create an aggregation query, set the read method's aggregators parameter to a list of aggregation functions. Each function is applied to all metrics configured for the query (see the columns parameter).</description></item><item><title>write Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/write/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/frames/tsdb/write/</guid><description>Description Writes (ingests) data from pandas DataFrames to a TSDB table.
Syntax write(backend, table, dfs, [labels=None, max_rows_in_msg=0, index_cols=None]) NoteThe method has additional parameters that aren't currently supported for the TSDB backend. Therefore, when calling the method, be sure to explicitly specify the names of all parameters after dfs.
Parameters backend | dfs | index_cols | labels | max_rows_in_msg | table
backend The backend type — &amp;quot;tsdb&amp;quot; for the TSDB backend.</description></item></channel></rss>