<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>_includes on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/</link><description>Recent content in _includes on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/frames-write-param-max-rows-in-msg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/frames-write-param-max-rows-in-msg/</guid><description> max_rows_in_msg The maximum number of DataFrame rows to write in each message (i.e., the size of the write chunks). When the value of this parameter is 0 (default), each DataFrame is written in a single message.
Type: int Requirement: Optional Default Value: 0</description></item><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/hw-cfgs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/hw-cfgs/</guid><description>The platform is available in two configurations, which differ in a variety of aspects, including the performance capacity, footprint, storage size, and scale capabilities:
Development Kit A single data-node and single application-node cluster implementation. This configuration is designed mainly for evaluation trials and doesn't include high availability (HA) or performance testing. Operational Cluster A scalable cluster implementation that is composed of multiple data and application nodes. This configuration was designed to achieve superior performance that enables real-time execution of analytics, machine-learning (ML), and artificial-intelligence (AI) applications in a production pipeline.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/hw-spec-min-storage-data-dependency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/hw-spec-min-storage-data-dependency/</guid><description>The exact amount of required storage depends on the amount of data that's being used in the platform; consult Iguazio's support team.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/section-post-install-https-certif-create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/section-post-install-https-certif-create/</guid><description>Creating an HTTPS Certificate In some cases, you might need to create an HTTPS certificate for your platform installation. For more information, contact Iguazio's support team.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/section-post-install-idp-import-from-ms-ad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/section-post-install-idp-import-from-ms-ad/</guid><description>Importing IdP Users and Groups from an Active Directory To import users and groups from an external Microsoft Active Directory, see the platform's IdP documentation. For additional assistance, contact Iguazio's support team.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/section-post-install-reg-custom-domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/section-post-install-reg-custom-domain/</guid><description>Registering a Custom Platform Domain If you chose to install the platform under a custom domain, you must register a few DNS records. If you need assistance, contact Iguazio's support team.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/users-container-envars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/users-container-envars/</guid><description> V3IO_USERNAME — set to the username of the running user of the Jupyter Notebook service. V3IO_HOME — set to the running-user directory in the &amp;quot;users&amp;quot; container — users/&amp;lt;running user&amp;gt;. V3IO_HOME_URL — set to the fully qualified v3io path to the running-user directory — v3io://users/&amp;lt;running user&amp;gt;.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/web-apis-urls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/_includes/web-apis-urls/</guid><description>Get this URL by copying the API URL of the web-APIs service (webapi) from the Services dashboard page. You can select between two types of URLs:
HTTPS Direct (recommended) — a URL of the format https://&amp;lt;tenant IP&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;web-APIs port&amp;gt;; for example, https://default-tenant.app.mycluster.iguazio.com:8443. Requests of this format are assigned to web-APIs servers by the DNS server of the web-APIs service: the DNS cache contains a random list of web-APIs servers, and the server attempts to assign each request to the first server on the list; if the first server becomes unavailable, the request is assigned to the next server in the list, and so forth.</description></item></channel></rss>