<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Azure Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/installationguides/</link><description>Recent content in Azure Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/installationguides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installing the Platform on a Microsoft Azure Cloud</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/installationguides/azure-installation-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/installationguides/azure-installation-guide/</guid><description>Overview This guide outlines the required steps for installing (deploying) an instance of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) to a Microsoft Azure cloud. When you complete the procedure, you'll have a platform instance running under your Azure account.
TroubleshootingIf you run into issues during the installation, check out the platform's Azure-installation troubleshooting guide. For further assistance, contact Iguazio's support team. Warning Provisioning of the servers is handled automatically by the platform installer (Provazio).</description></item><item><title>Installing the Platform on a Microsoft Azure Cloud With AKS</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/installationguides/azure-installation-guide-aks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/installationguides/azure-installation-guide-aks/</guid><description>Overview This guide outlines the required steps for installing (deploying) an instance of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) to a Microsoft Azure cloud. When you complete the procedure, you will have a platform instance running under your Azure account.
TroubleshootingIf you run into issues during the installation, see the platform's Azure-installation troubleshooting guide. For further assistance, contact Iguazio's support team. Warning Provisioning of the servers is handled automatically by the platform installer (Provazio).</description></item></channel></rss>