<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NoSQL Backend on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/</link><description>Recent content in NoSQL Backend on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>delete Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/delete/</guid><description>Description Deletes a NoSQL table or or specific table items.
Note In the current release, to delete a partitioned table you need to delete each table partition separately, by issuing multiple delete calls and setting the table parameter in each call to the path to a different partition directory. After deleting all the partitions, you can call the delete method with the root table path to delete the table's schema file and complete the deletion.</description></item><item><title>execute Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/execute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/execute/</guid><description>Description Executes the specified command. This method is used to extend the basic functionality of the other client methods. Currently, the NoSQL backend supports an infer_schema command with an infer alias for inferring the table schema.
Syntax execute(backend, table, command=&amp;#34;&amp;#34; NoteThe method has additional parameters that aren't currently supported for the NoSQL backend. Therefore, when calling the method, be sure to explicitly specify the names of all parameters after table.</description></item><item><title>Overview of the Frames NoSQL Backend</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/overview/</guid><description>Introduction The NoSQL backend of the Frames API supports Client methods and commands for working with NoSQL data in the platform using the NoSQL database service, which enables storing and consuming data in a tabular format. For more information, see Working with NoSQL Data.
To add, replace, or update a table item, use the write method.
To create a table, just begin adding items. The table will be created automatically with the first item that you add.</description></item><item><title>read Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/read/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/read/</guid><description>Description Reads (consumes) item attributes from a NoSQL table into pandas DataFrames.
NoteBy default, the method returns all user attributes (columns) of all the items (rows) in the specified NoSQL table. You can optionally restrict the read query by setting the filter parameter to a filter expression that restricts which items to read and/or setting the columns parameter to a list of item attributes to return for the read items (as restricted by the filter expression, if set).</description></item><item><title>write Method</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/write/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/frames/nosql/write/</guid><description>Description Writes (ingests) data from pandas DataFrames to a NoSQL table.
Note NoSQL tables in the platform don't need to be created prior to ingestion. When writing (ingesting) data into a table that doesn't exist, the table and all directories in the specified path are automatically created. When updating a table item (i.e., when writing an item with the same primary-key attribute value as an existing table item), the existing item is overwritten and replaced with the written item.</description></item></channel></rss>