<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GCP Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/</link><description>Recent content in GCP Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Calculating Required Infrastructure Resources (GCP)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/resources-calculate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/resources-calculate/</guid><description>Allocated Infrastructure Resources When the platform is installed, it creates the following resources. Take this into account when selecting your installation configuration.
You also need to consider the GCP quotas (known as limits) for your GCP account.
Type Amount When Notes Data node 1 or 3 Always Instance type n2-highmem-16. High-availability (HA) requires three nodes. Application node 1 or more Always Instance type c2-standard-16 or larger. High-availability (HA) requires at least three nodes.</description></item><item><title>Creating a GCP Service Account</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/service-account-create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/service-account-create/</guid><description>Overview When installing the platform, a service account with Owner permissions needs to be created.
Step 1: GCP Login Log into your GCP Management Console and select the IAM &amp;amp; Admin section. Step 2: Create a Service Account In the side navigation menu, select Service Accounts, and then select Create Service Account. Type a name and description, then click Create. Step 3: Set Owner Permissions In the Grant this service account access to project section, choose Owner.</description></item><item><title>Post-Installation Steps (GCP)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/post-install-steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/howto/post-install-steps/</guid><description>Overview After following the platform's GCP cloud installation guide, you should have a running instance of the platform in your GCP cloud. In some cases, additional post-deployment steps are required before you can properly use the platform, as outlined in this guide.
Registering a Custom Platform Domain If you chose to install the platform under a custom domain, you must register a few DNS records. If you need assistance, contact Iguazio's support team.</description></item></channel></rss>