<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Objects on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/data-layer/objects/</link><description>Recent content in Data Objects on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/data-layer/objects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ingesting and Consuming Files</title><link>/data-layer/objects/ingest-n-consume-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/objects/ingest-n-consume-files/</guid><description>&amp;lt;!-- JillG-9-9-21 Zeppelin removed from SW, no plan to return it. The #convert-csv-to-nosql section in this file now points to https://github.com/v3io/tutorials/blob/3.x/data-ingestion-and-preparation/basic-data-ingestion-and-preparation.ipynb Overview This tutorial demonstrates how to ingest (write) a new file object to a data container in the platform, and consume (read) an ingested file, either from the dashboard or by using the Simple-Object Web API. The tutorial also demonstrates how to convert a CSV file to a NoSQL table by using the Spark SQL and DataFrames API.</description></item><item><title>Objects Attributes</title><link>/data-layer/objects/attributes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/objects/attributes/</guid><description>Introduction All data objects in the platform have attributes. An attribute provides information (metadata) about an object. NoSQL table-item attributes in the platform are the equivalent of columns in standard NoSQL databases. See Working with NoSQL Data, including a terminology comparison. For the supported attribute data types, see the Attribute Data Types Reference.
Attribute Types Attributes are classified into three logical types:
User attributes Attributes that the user assigns to a data object using the platform APIs.</description></item></channel></rss>