<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform Services on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/</link><description>Recent content in Platform Services on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding Grafana Dashboards</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/grafana-dashboards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/grafana-dashboards/</guid><description>Overview The platform includes a pre-deployed version of the open-source Grafana analytics and monitoring platform. For detailed information about working with Grafana, see the Grafana documentation. Grafana allows the creation of custom web dashboards that visualize real-time data queries. This tutorial outlines the steps for creating your own Grafana dashboard for querying data in the your cluster's data containers by using the custom iguazio Grafana data source, or by using a Prometheus data source for running Prometheus queries on platform TSDB tables.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring Platform Services</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/monitoring-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/monitoring-services/</guid><description>The Monitoring Application Service and Grafana Dashboards The platform has a default (pre-deployed) tenant-wide monitoring application service (monitoring) for monitoring application services and gathering performance statistics and additional data. This service is enabled by default.
All Grafana user services in the platform that are created or restarted after the monitoring service is enabled have a private dashboards directory that contains the following predefined dashboards. The dashboards visualize data gathered by the monitoring service for application services of the parent tenant:</description></item><item><title>Working with Services</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/fundamentals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/services/fundamentals/</guid><description>Overview The Services page of the platform dashboard displays information about running application services — which include both default services that are created as part of the platform's deployment (such as the web-APIs or Presto services) and user-defined services (such as Spark or Jupyter Notebook). A service administrator can create, delete, enable, disable, restart, and configure application services, and view service logs. A user-defined service is typically assigned to a specific running user and can also optionally be shared with all other users in the same tenant.</description></item></channel></rss>