<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform Users and Security on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/users-and-security/</link><description>Recent content in Platform Users and Security on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/users-and-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Platform Users</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/users-and-security/users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/users-and-security/users/</guid><description>Overview To use the platform, you must be logged in as a user with relevant permissions. A user can optionally be a member of one or more user groups. When a user is a member of multiple groups, one of the groups is defined as the user's primary group.
The platform has several predefined users. A security administrator — which is any user with the Security Admin management policy, including the predefined security_admin user — can manage platform users and user groups.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/users-and-security/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/users-and-security/security/</guid><description>Overview The platform implements multiple mechanisms to secure access to resources and keep your data safe. All user and security management is done under a single pane of glass: the configuration is done in one place, in the user-friendly graphical platform dashboard, and applied across all platform interfaces. The result is a significantly simplified, yet robust, data-security solution that helps organizations meet their compliance objectives.
The platform allows you to define local users and import users from an external identity provider (IdP), authenticate user identities, and control users' access to resources, including the ability to define fine-grained data-access policies.</description></item></channel></rss>