<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/intro/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>APIs Overview</title><link>/intro/apis-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/intro/apis-overview/</guid><description>The platform exposes the following application programming interfaces (APIs).
Data science and MLOps APIs — the platform integrates Iguazio's open-source MLRun machine-learning operations (MLOps) orchestration framework and Nuclio serverless-functions framework. For detailed information about these frameworks and their APIs, see Data Science and MLOps.
Data-layer APIs — the platform exposes multiple APIs for working with data of all types — NoSQL (&amp;quot;key-value&amp;quot;) databases, time-series databases (TSDBs), streams, and simple objects (files) — including the following APIs.</description></item><item><title>High Availability (HA)</title><link>/intro/high-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/intro/high-availability/</guid><description>Overview The Operational Cluster configuration of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) is a high-availability (HA) cluster. It was designed from the ground up as a shared-nothing (SN) architecture — a distributed architecture with no single point of failure (SPOF). Every cluster has at least three data nodes and supports data replication, ensuring high availability.
Data-Replication and Failover The platform's data-distribution architecture ensures that there are always two copies of each data element.</description></item><item><title>Iguazio Trial Quick-Start</title><link>/intro/trial-qs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/intro/trial-qs/</guid><description>Get ready to start your free evaluation of the MLOps Platform ... .
Overview Iguazio trial is a free evaluation of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) from within a cloud environment that doesn't require any user installations or configurations. When you register to the trial, you receive your own cluster — a dedicated cloud instance of the platform. To register for a free evaluation, click here or select the Try Iguazio for free button on the Iguazio web site.</description></item><item><title>In-Depth Platform Overview</title><link>/intro/product-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/intro/product-overview/</guid><description>Overview This document provides an in-depth overview of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) and how to use it to implement a full data science workflow.
NoteStart out by first reading the Introducing the Platform introduction and high-level overview. The platform uses Kubernetes (k8s) as the baseline cluster manager, and deploys various application microservices on top of Kubernetes to address different data science tasks. Most of the provided services support scaling out and GPU acceleration and have a secure and low-latency access to the platform's shared data store and file system, enabling high performance and scalability with maximum resource efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Platform</title><link>/intro/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/intro/introduction/</guid><description>Welcome to the Iguazio Data Science Platform An initial introduction to the Iguazio Data Science platform and the platform tutorials
Platform Overview Data Science Workflow The Tutorial Notebooks Getting-Started Tutorial End-to-End Use-Case Application and How-To Demos Installing and Updating the MLRun Python Package Data Ingestion and Preparation Additional platform Resources Miscellaneous
Platform Overview The Iguazio Data Science platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) is a fully integrated and secure data science platform as a service (PaaS), which simplifies development, accelerates performance, facilitates collaboration, and addresses operational challenges.</description></item><item><title>The Platform Dashboard (UI)</title><link>/intro/ui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/intro/ui/</guid><description>The dashboard is the platform's graphical user interface and is also your entry point to your platform cluster. Go to the dashboard URL from any web browser and log in with your platform login credentials. The dashboard allows managing and monitoring platform activity. You can navigate the dashboard pages from the side navigation menu. NoteSome areas of the dashboard and some UI operations might not be available to you, depending on your user permissions.</description></item></channel></rss>