<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Post-Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/</link><description>Recent content in Post-Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuring Environmental Variables</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/env_vars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/env_vars/</guid><description>Overview You can configure environmental variables, as key-value pairs, for Jupyter and Web Shell services. The values are applied to every instance of these services. You can define any variable that is supported by these services.
After you configure global environmental variables, you can override the global value for an individual Jupyter service in the Services page. The environmental variables for other services cannot be overridden.
Configuring environmental variables in the Dashboard Follow these steps to configure environmental variables for your cluster:</description></item><item><title>Configuring the DNS Server</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/dns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/dns/</guid><description>Overview Application services in the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) clusters run on top of Kubernetes (see The Platform's Application Services). The services are accessed via Kubernetes ingresses, which act as gateways that allow access to cluster applications and internal services through service URLs. The platform uses the CoreDNS DNS server to resolve cluster service URLs and map them to internal service IP addresses. The cluster's DNS server should be configured to use conditional forwarding, so that DNS queries that contain the domain name of the cluster, and only such queries, are forwarded to the platform for resolution.</description></item><item><title>Configuring the Python Repositories</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/python_vars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/python_vars/</guid><description>Overview You can define pip and Conda key-value pairs as:
Environmental variables for shell and Jupyter Default build arguments for Nuclio and MLRun The values are applied to every instance of these services. You can define any variable that is supported by pip or Conda. Changing the Pypi server URL causes a restart of Jupyter, MLRun, Nuclio, and Shell, services.
Configuring pip and Conda environmental variables in the Dashboard To configure pip and Conda environmental variables for your cluster:</description></item><item><title>Configuring the SMTP Server</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/smtp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/post-deployment-howtos/smtp/</guid><description>Overview The platform sends email messages for different purposes, such as password generation and call home functionality. To support this, the platform clusters needs to be configured to work with a Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP) server that will be used for sending the email messages.
Prerequisites The following prerequisites must be filled to successfully configure an SMTP server for your cluster:
There must be an SMTP server with connectivity to the cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>