<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Amazon Web Services (AWS) Cloud Deployment on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/</link><description>Recent content in Amazon Web Services (AWS) Cloud Deployment on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS Cloud Deployment Specifications</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/aws-hw-spec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/aws-hw-spec/</guid><description>Overview This document lists the hardware specifications for deployment of version 3.2.1 of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) on the Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud; for details, refer to the AWS documentation.
Note All references to AWS cloud apply also to AWS Outposts, except where otherwise specified. AWS platform deployments also require an Elastic IP address. For more information, see the AWS documentation. All capacity calculations in the hardware specifications are performed using the base-10 (decimal) number system.</description></item><item><title>Installing the Platform on an AWS Cloud</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/installationguides/aws-installation-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/installationguides/aws-installation-guide/</guid><description>Overview This guide outlines the required steps for installing (deploying) an instance of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) to an Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud (including AWS Outposts). When you complete the procedure, you'll have a platform instance running under your AWS account. The installation is done by using the platform installer — Provazio — with your AWS credentials.
Note The deployment procedure requires proficiency in Systems Operations on AWS, and is typically completed in 1–2 hours.</description></item></channel></rss>