<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Azure Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/</link><description>Recent content in Azure Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Post-Installation Steps (Azure)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/post-install-steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/post-install-steps/</guid><description>Overview After following the platform's Azure cloud installation guide, you should have a running instance of the platform in your Azure cloud. In some cases, additional post-deployment steps are required before you can properly use the platform, as outlined in this guide.
Registering a Custom Platform Domain If you chose to install the platform under a custom domain, you must register a few DNS records. If you need assistance, contact Iguazio's support team.</description></item><item><title>Calculating Required Infrastructure Resources (Azure)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/resources-calculate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/resources-calculate/</guid><description>Allocated Infrastructure Resources When the platform is installed, it creates the following resources. Take this into account when selecting your installation configuration. Type Amount When Notes Data node 1 or 3 Always Azure instance type (VM size) Standard_L16s_v2. High-availability (HA) requires three nodes. Data-cluster application security group 1 per data cluster Always Application node 1 or more Always Azure instance type (VM size) Standard_D16s_v3 or larger or NCv3-series (GPU optimized).</description></item><item><title>Network Security Groups Configuration (Azure)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/network-security-groups-cfg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/network-security-groups-cfg/</guid><description>Overview As part of the platform installation, a set of security groups are configured to control access at the network level (&amp;quot;network security groups&amp;quot;), in addition to the platform's application-level authentication. These groups can be reconfigured manually at any time after the installation. When the platform is created with private IPs only, security groups are usually not much of a concern. However, it's crucial to properly set up the security groups when the platform is assigned public IP addresses.</description></item><item><title>Pre-Installation Steps Using the Azure CLI</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/pre-install-steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/pre-install-steps/</guid><description>Before you install an instance of the platform to an Azure cloud, perform the pre-installation steps outlined in this guide.
Install the Azure CLI Install the Azure CLI (az) by following the instructions in the Azure documentation. When you're done, run the following command from a command-line shell to verify that the CLI is functioning properly:
az login This command should open an Azure portal login screen. Log into your Azure account and run the following command to list all the existing resource groups under your account:</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting Azure Cloud Installations</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/troubleshoot-install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/azure/howto/troubleshoot-install/</guid><description>Overview The platform installation is done using two sequential deployments. The first deployment creates a virtual network (optional), an empty security group, and a small installer virtual machine (&amp;quot;the installer VM&amp;quot;). After the installer VM initializes, the platform installer (&amp;quot;Provazio&amp;quot;) is executed by running a script that launches a Docker image (quay.io/iguazio/provazio-dashboard:az-market-0) that contains the installer. The script generates a system configuration and posts it to Provazio. Provazio then starts the installation process according to the system configuration, and creates a second deployment that's responsible for bringing up the infrastructure.</description></item></channel></rss>