<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data-Layer References on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Data-Layer References on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NoSQL Table Schema Reference</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/nosql-table-schema/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/nosql-table-schema/</guid><description>Overview To support reading and writing NoSQL data using structured-data interfaces — such as Spark DataFrames, Presto, and V3IO Frames (&amp;quot;Frames&amp;quot;) — the platform uses a schema file that defines the schema of the data structure. When writing NoSQL data in the platform using a Spark or Frames DataFrame, the schema of the data table is automatically identified and saved and then retrieved when using a structure-data interface to read data from the same table (unless you explicitly define the schema for the read operation).</description></item><item><title>Reserved Names</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/reserved-names/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/reserved-names/</guid><description>Overview This reference lists reserved names in the platform's data=layer APIs. Don't use these names for your custom components such as for attribute names. For additional restrictions, see the Software Specifications and Restrictions. NoteThe reserved names are case insensitive. For example, for the reserved keyword set, also avoid using SET or Set. Expressions All expression keywords, including the following, are reserved names in the platform:
Logical operators Update-expression keywords Logical Operators and in or out NoteFor more information, see the Logical Operators expressions reference.</description></item><item><title>System-Attributes Reference</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/system-attributes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/reference/system-attributes/</guid><description>The platform defines the following object (item) system attributes. For more information, see the description of system attributes in the attribute-types introduction.
NoteThe names of the predefined system attributes are reserved names in the platform. For more information, see Reserved Names. Attribute Description __name Object name, which uniquely identifies the object within a collection and serves as the value of the object's primary key. See Object Names and Primary Keys.</description></item></channel></rss>