<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Expressions Reference on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/data-layer/reference/expressions/</link><description>Recent content in Expressions Reference on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/data-layer/reference/expressions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Condition Expression</title><link>/data-layer/reference/expressions/condition-expression/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/expressions/condition-expression/</guid><description>Overview A condition expression is an expression that defines a condition for executing an operation, based on the attributes of the items against which the expression is evaluated. For example, the NoSQL Web API UpdateItem operation receives an optional condition-expression request parameter (ConditionExpression) that defines a condition that determines whether to update the item or which update expression to use in the case of an if-then-else update.
Arrays SupportIn the current release, the support for array attributes and the use of array operators and functions in expressions is restricted to the web APIs.</description></item><item><title>Expressions Overview</title><link>/data-layer/reference/expressions/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/expressions/overview/</guid><description>The platform APIs support the use of expressions to define execution logic and enhance the support for working with NoSQL items (objects) and their attributes.
Condition expressions define a logical condition for performing a specific operation. Update expressions can be used to add and initialize item attributes, update the values of existing attributes or elements in an array attribute, or remove (delete) attributes. This reference outlines the supported expressions and their syntax.</description></item><item><title>Update Expression</title><link>/data-layer/reference/expressions/update-expression/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/data-layer/reference/expressions/update-expression/</guid><description>Overview An update expression is an expression that is used to update the attributes of an item. This includes adding attributes and initializing their values, changing the value of existing attributes, or removing (deleting) item attributes. For example, the NoSQL Web API UpdateItem operation receives an update-expression request parameter (UpdateExpression), and optionally also an alternate update-expression parameter for an if-then-else update (AlternateUpdateExpression), that define which item attributes to update and how to update them.</description></item></channel></rss>