<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VMware vSphere Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/</link><description>Recent content in VMware vSphere Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Attaching Data Disks to the Data-Node VMs (vSphere)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/data-disks-attach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/data-disks-attach/</guid><description>Overview The platform installation requires that you attach data disks (block-storage devices) of a specific type and minimal capacity, which are configured with raw device mapping (RDM), directly to each of the platform's data-node VMs (&amp;quot;the data nodes&amp;quot;), as outlined in this guide.
Prerequisites Before you begin, ensure that you have the following:
Administrative access to a platform vSphere cluster with the required networks configuration (see Configuring Virtual Networking (vSphere)) and deployed VMs for each of the platform nodes (see Deploying the Platform Nodes (vSphere)).</description></item><item><title>Configuring IP Addresses (vSphere)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/ips-cfg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/ips-cfg/</guid><description>Overview To allow the platform installer (Provazio) to connect to the platform's data and application nodes, you need to configure IP addresses for the management network (&amp;quot;management IP addresses&amp;quot;) on the platform's node VMs, as outlined in this guides.
Prerequisites Before you begin, ensure that you have the following:
Administrative access to a platform vSphere cluster with the required networks configuration (see Configuring Virtual Networking (vSphere)) and deployed VMs for each of the platform nodes (see Deploying the Platform Nodes (vSphere)).</description></item><item><title>Configuring Virtual Networking (vSphere)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/network-cfg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/network-cfg/</guid><description>Overview The platform's data and application node VMs ("the platform nodes") are connected through three networks: Management network &amp;mdash; used for user access to the platform dashboard and for direct access the platform nodes. Data-path (client) network &amp;mdash; used for internal communication among the data and application nodes. Interconnect network &amp;mdash; used for internal communication among the data nodes. To allow proper communication, you need to create and map virtual network switches (vSwitches) for these networks, as outlined in this guide.</description></item><item><title>Deploying the Platform Nodes (vSphere)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/vms-deploy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/vms-deploy/</guid><description>Overview To install (deploy) an instance of the platform on a VMware vSphere cluster, you need to deploy virtual machines (VMs) that will serve as the platform's data and application nodes. The nodes can reside on the same VMware ESXi hypervisor host machine (&amp;quot;ESXi host&amp;quot;) or on different ESXi hosts, as long as every node VM meets the required hardware specifications (see the prerequisites in this guide and the On-Prem Deployment Specifications.</description></item><item><title>Installing the Platform without an Internet Connection (Offline Installation) (vSphere)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/offline-install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/offline-install/</guid><description>Overview Installing (deploying) the platform on virtual machines (VMs) in environments without an internet connection (a.k.a. &amp;quot;dark sites&amp;quot;) requires a variation on the online procedure that's described in the vSphere Installation Guide, as outlined in this guide.
Prerequisites Before you begin, ensure that you have the following:
A platform installation package (&amp;lt;build name&amp;gt;.tar.gz), received from Iguazio. A preloaded Provazio dashboard Docker image (gcr.io/iguazio/provazio-dashboard:stable), received from Iguazio as an image archive (provazio-latest.</description></item><item><title>Post-Installation Steps (vSphere)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/post-install-steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/on-prem/vm/vmware/howto/post-install-steps/</guid><description>Overview After following the VMware vSphere installation guide, you should have a running instance of the platform on your vSphere cluster. In some cases, additional post-deployment steps are required before you can properly use the platform, as outlined in this guide.
Registering a Custom Platform Domain If you chose to install the platform under a custom domain, you must register a few DNS records. If you need assistance, contact Iguazio's support team.</description></item></channel></rss>