<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Expression Functions on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/</link><description>Recent content in Expression Functions on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Array Functions</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/array-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/array-functions/</guid><description>Note In the current release, the support for array attributes and the use of array operators and functions in expressions is restricted to the web APIs.
See also the array support of the max and min functions.
length length(ARRAY) Returns the length of the provided array or array slice (ARRAY) — i.e., the number of elements in the array or slice. The parameter can be the name of an array attribute (ARRAY-ATTRIBUTE), or a slice of an array attribute that indicates the zero-based index range of the array elements to compare (ARRAY-ATTRIBUTE[istart.</description></item><item><title>Expression String Functions</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/string-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/string-functions/</guid><description>The following Boolean string-comparison functions are supported in expressions. All functions receive two string parameters. Each parameter can be provided either as a constant literal string (LITERAL), or as an attribute variable (ATTRIBUTE) that represents a string attribute (of type &amp;quot;S&amp;quot;) whose value will be used in the comparison.
ends ends(s1, s2) Checks whether the first string (s1) ends with the second string (s2).
For example, ends('4-Jun-2018', year) returns true for a year string attribute whose value is &amp;quot;2018&amp;quot;.</description></item><item><title>If Exists/Not-Exists Expression Functions</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/exists-n-not-exists-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/exists-n-not-exists-functions/</guid><description>exists exists(ATTRIBUTE) Checks whether an attribute with the specified name (ATTRIBUTE — see Attribute Variables) exists in the evaluated item.
For example, exists(Vendor) returns true if the evaluated item has a Vendor attribute.
if_not_exists if_not_exists(ATTRIBUTE, VALUE) If the specified attribute (ATTRIBUTE — see Attribute Variables) exists, the function returns its value. Otherwise, the function returns the default value specified in the VALUE parameter.
For example, a &amp;quot;SET lastName = if_not_exists(lastName, '')&amp;quot; update expression creates a lastName attribute and initializes its value to an empty string, provided the attribute doesn't already exist; if the attribute exists, it will be reassigned its current value (i.</description></item><item><title>Maximal-/Minimal-Value Expression Functions</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/min-max-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/reference/expressions/functions/min-max-functions/</guid><description>Note min and max are supported in update expressions.
Regarding the use of the min and max functions with arrays, note that in the current release this is restricted to the web APIs.
max The max function supports the following variations:
Simple-values comparison Array-elements comparison Compare Simple Values max(a, b) When max receives two parameters, it returns the highest (maximal) parameter value.</description></item></channel></rss>