<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Google Cloud Deployment on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/</link><description>Recent content in Google Cloud Deployment on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GCP Deployment Specifications</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/gcp-hw-spec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/gcp-hw-spec/</guid><description>Overview This document lists the hardware specifications for deployment of version 3.2.1 of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) on Google Cloud, also known as Google Cloud Platform (GCP); for details, refer to the Google Cloud Compute Engine documentation.
NoteAll capacity calculations in the hardware specifications are performed using the base-10 (decimal) number system. For example, 1 TB = 1,000,000,000,000 bytes. Warning Provisioning of the servers is handled automatically by the platform installer (Provazio).</description></item><item><title>Installing the Platform on Google Cloud Platform (GCP)</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/gcp-installation-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/gcp/gcp-installation-guide/</guid><description>Overview This guide outlines the required steps for installing (deploying) an instance of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) to Google Cloud Platform (GCP). When you complete the procedure, you'll have a platform instance running under your GCP account. Install the platform with the Provazio installer, with your GCP credentials.
Warning Provisioning of the servers is handled automatically by the platform installer (Provazio). Don't attempt to provision the servers manually prior to the deployment.</description></item></channel></rss>