<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deployment and Specifications on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/</link><description>Recent content in Deployment and Specifications on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/cluster-mgmt/deployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hardware-Configuration and Deployment Options</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cfg-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cfg-options/</guid><description>Overview The MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;) provides enterprises with the flexibility to run applications on-premises (&amp;quot;on-prem&amp;quot;) or in an edge or hybrid cloud architecture. The platform was built from the ground up to maximize CPU utilization and leverage the benefits of non-volatile memory, 100 GbE remote direct memory access (RDMA), flash memory, and dense storage. This design enables the platform to achieve extreme performance while maintaining data consistency, at the lowest cost.</description></item><item><title>Software Specifications and Restrictions</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/sw-specifications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/sw-specifications/</guid><description>Following is a list of software specifications and restrictions for version 3.2.1 of the MLOps Platform (&amp;quot;the platform&amp;quot;). For a list of reserved names in the platform, see the reserved-names reference. For a list of known issues for the current release, see the release notes. (Note: For amount values, M = million; B = billion.)
ConfidentialityThe documentation in this section is confidential under the Iguazio End User License Agreement.</description></item><item><title>Support and Certification Matrix</title><link>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/support-matrix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cluster-mgmt/deployment/support-matrix/</guid><description>Overview The platform comes pre-deployed with proprietary and third-party open-source tools and libraries that are exposed as application services that are managed using Kubernetes. Relevant services can be viewed and managed by users from the platform dashboard using a self-service model. (Note that some services that don't require user intervention aren't visible in the dashboard.) Users can also enhance their development experience by independently installing additional software and run it on top of the platform services.</description></item></channel></rss>