<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Using the Presto SQL-Query Engine on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/presto/</link><description>Recent content in Using the Presto SQL-Query Engine on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/presto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduciton to Using Presto in the Platform</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/presto/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/presto/overview/</guid><description>Introduction You can use the Presto open-source distributed SQL query engine to run interactive SQL queries and perform high-performance low-latency interactive analytics on data that is stored in the platform. Running Presto over the platform's data services enables you to filter data as close as possible to the source. The platform's Iguazio Presto connector defines a custom data source that enables you to use Presto to query data in the platform's NoSQL store — including support for table partitioning, predicate pushdown, column pruning, and performing optimized item-specific and range-scan queries.</description></item><item><title>The Presto CLI</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/presto/presto-cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/data-layer/presto/presto-cli/</guid><description>Overview The web-based shell service and the terminals of the Jupyter Notebook service are automatically connected to the Presto service and include a copy of the native Presto command-line interface (CLI) — presto-cli — which you can use to query data in the platform. The native Presto CLI is found in the /usr/local/bin directory, which is included in the environment path ($PATH) to simplify execution from any directory. To facilitate using Presto with the Iguazio Presto connector to query NoSQL tables in the platform's data containers, the environment path also contains a presto wrapper that preconfigures your cluster's Presto server URL, the v3io catalog, the Presto user's username and password (platform access key), and the Presto Java TrustStore file and password.</description></item></channel></rss>