<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cluster-Management REST APIs Reference on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/</link><description>Recent content in Cluster-Management REST APIs Reference on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>General Management-API Structure</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/general-api-structure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/general-api-structure/</guid><description>The management APIs are RESTful APIs that use a subset of the JSON API specification to represent request and response data.
Request Syntax The management-API operations are HTTP requests that you send to a dashboard endpoint using an appropriate HTTP method (such as GET or POST). Data parameters (where required) are passed within the request's HTTP body, in JSON format. The requests conform to the following general format:
&amp;lt;method&amp;gt; /&amp;lt;resource&amp;gt; HTTP/1.</description></item><item><title>Overview of the Cluster-Management REST APIs</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/reference/management-apis/overview/</guid><description>The platform's cluster-management REST APIs (&amp;quot;the management APIs&amp;quot;) provide an alternative to using the dashboard to perform management operations — such as containers management, system administration, and security operations (including management of users, groups, tenants, and data-access polices). The management-APIs are exposed as /api/&amp;lt;API ID&amp;gt; endpoints (for example, /api/containers).
This section describes the general structure of management-API requests and responses, and provides a reference of the following management APIs:
Sessions API for supporting user authentication and authorization.</description></item></channel></rss>