<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Containers on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/</link><description>Recent content in Data Containers on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Container Names and IDs</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/container-names/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/container-names/</guid><description>Container Names Every container has a name, which is a user-assigned string that uniquely identifies the container within its tenant and in the dashboard.
Container-Name Restrictions Container names are subject to the general file-system naming restrictions and the following additional restrictions:
Contain only the following characters:
Lowercase letters (a–z) and numeric digits (0–9) Hyphens (-) Underscores (_) Begin and end with a lowercase letter (a–z) or a numeric digit (0–9)</description></item><item><title>The Predefined Containers</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/predefined-containers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/predefined-containers/</guid><description>The standard platform installations have several predefined containers — &amp;quot;users&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;projects&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;bigdata&amp;quot;.
The &amp;quot;users&amp;quot; Container The &amp;quot;users&amp;quot; container is designed to provide individual user development environments and is used by the platform to manage application services. When creating a new web-based shel or Jupyter Notebook, the platform automatically creates a &amp;lt;username&amp;gt; directory for the service's running user in This container (if it doesn't already exist). This directory serves as the home directory of the service environment ($HOME) and is used to store different files for managing the service.</description></item><item><title>Working with Data Containers</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/working-with-containers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/containers/working-with-containers/</guid><description>Overview This tutorial outlines different methods for performing basic data-container tasks in the platform — listing the existing containers, creating and deleting containers and container directories, and browsing container contents.
Before You Begin This tutorial demonstrates how to perform basic tasks using different platform interfaces — dashboard, file system, web APIs, and cluster-management APIs.
To use the file-system interface, you need to create a command-line service from which to run your code — such as a web-based shell, or Jupyter Notebook.</description></item></channel></rss>