<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AWS Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/</link><description>Recent content in AWS Cloud Deployment How-Tos on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Post-Installation Steps (AWS)</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/post-install-steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/post-install-steps/</guid><description>Overview After following the platform's AWS cloud installation guide, you should have a running instance of the platform in your AWS cloud. In some cases, additional post-deployment steps are required before you can properly use the platform, as outlined in this guide.
Registering a Custom Platform Domain If you chose to install the platform under a custom domain, you must register a few DNS records. If you need assistance, contact Iguazio's support team.</description></item><item><title>Calculating Required Infrastructure Resources (AWS)</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/resources-calculate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/resources-calculate/</guid><description>Allocated Infrastructure Resources When the platform is installed, it creates the following resources. Take this into account when selecting your installation configuration. Note that you also need to consider the service quotas (a.k.a. limits) for your AWS account. Type Amount When Notes Data node 1 or 3 Always EC2 instance type i3.2xlarge, i3.4xlarge or i3.8xlarge. High-availability (HA) requires three nodes. Data auto-scaling group 1 Always Application node 1 or more Always EC2 CPU instance type m5.</description></item><item><title>Configuring VPC Subnet Allocation of Public IP Addresses (AWS)</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/subnet-public-ips-alloc-cfg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/subnet-public-ips-alloc-cfg/</guid><description>Overview When installing an instance of the platform with public IP addresses, you must enable and configure allocation of public IP addresses for one or more subnets of the AWS virtual private cloud (VPC) in which the platform will be installed, as outlined in this guide.
Step 1: AWS Login Log into your AWS Management Console and select the VPC service. Step 2: Subnets Selection Under Subnets, select the subnet (or subnets) in which you plan to install the platform.</description></item><item><title>Creating an AWS IAM Role and Instance Profile</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/iam-role-n-instance-profile-create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/iam-role-n-instance-profile-create/</guid><description>Overview At times, the platform's EC2 instances need to access the AWS API. For example, to achieve high availability, the instances within a cluster share a single secondary IP address, which is allocated to a specific instance at any given moment. Migrating this secondary IP to another instance requires an AWS API call to update the internal AWS network. To perform an AWS API call, the platform must be authenticated using AWS credentials with the necessary permissions for performing this operation.</description></item><item><title>Creating an AWS IAM User</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/iam-user-create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/iam-user-create/</guid><description>Overview When installing the platform, the installation needs the credentials of your AWS account to create the required infrastructure. This guide walks you through the steps for creating a restricted AWS IAM user, which has only the minimal set of permissions that are required for the installation. You'll need to provide the credentials of this user as part of the platform installation, as outlined in the platform's AWS cloud installation guide.</description></item><item><title>Deploying an Amazon EKS Application Cluster</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/eks-app-cluster-deploy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/eks-app-cluster-deploy/</guid><description>Overview This guide describes how to install (deploy) MLOps Platform application nodes to Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) in an AWS cloud — i.e., deploy an AWS EKS platform application cluster.
Configuring an EKS Application Cluster On the Clusters page of the platform installer (Provazio), fill in the EKS related configuration parameters, and then select Next.
Kubernetes Kind Set this to New EKS Cluster.</description></item><item><title>Network Security Groups Configuration (AWS)</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/network-security-groups-cfg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/cluster-mgmt/deployment/cloud/aws/howto/network-security-groups-cfg/</guid><description>Overview As part of the platform installation, a set of security groups are configured to control access at the network level (&amp;quot;network security groups&amp;quot;), in addition to the platform's application-level authentication. These groups can be reconfigured manually at any time after the installation. When the platform is created with private IPs only, security groups are usually not much of a concern. However, it's crucial to properly set up the security groups when the platform is assigned public IP addresses.</description></item></channel></rss>