<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Time-Series Databases (TSDB) on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/tsdb/</link><description>Recent content in Time-Series Databases (TSDB) on Iguazio MLOps Platform Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/tsdb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The V3IO TSDB CLI (tsdbctl)</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/tsdb/tsdb-cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/tsdb/tsdb-cli/</guid><description>Overview The V3IO TSDB includes the V3IO TSDB command-line interface (&amp;quot;the TSDB CLI&amp;quot;), which enables users to easily create, update, query, and delete time-series databases (TSDBs), as demonstrated in this tutorial. Before you get started, read the setup and usage information in this section and review the TSDB software specifications and restrictions.
Setup Reference Mandatory Command Configurations Using a Configuration File Setup The TSDB CLI can be run locally on a platform application cluster or remotely from any computer with a network connection to the cluster.</description></item><item><title>Working with Time-Series Databases (TSDBs)</title><link>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/tsdb/working-with-tsdbs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/jasonnIguazio/ghpages-doc-site/data-layer/tsdb/working-with-tsdbs/</guid><description>The platform comes pre-deployed with the Iguazio V3IO TSDB library (&amp;quot;V3IO TSDB&amp;quot;) for working with data in time-series databases (TSDBs). This library exposes a high-performance API for creating, updating, querying, and deleting time series databases. You can access the API with:
The V3IO TSDB CLI tool (tsdbctl) that is pre-deployed as part of the default platform installation, for seamless integration with the platform. The TSDB APIs included in the pre-deployed platform application services V3IO Frames, which expose a Python API.</description></item></channel></rss>